{"data":[{"question":"He was a very unpopular man in the village. Nobody ________ him.","a":"quarrelled","b":"hated","c":"liked","d":"objected","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Like sbd: to think that someone is nice or enjoy being with them.\u00a0\n- Quarrel with sbd; object sth.\u00a0\n- Hate: the meaning is not suitable with this sentence.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The country was in total ________ as all of the political factions attempted to gain control after the revolution.","a":"confusion","b":"confustion","c":"confusment","d":"confusian","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Confusion(noun): a situation in which someone wrongly thinks that a person or thing is someone or something else.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"In order to make a good ________ at a job interview, you should prepare well for the interview.","a":"impressment","b":"impressian","c":"impresstion","d":"impression","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Make a good impression: to make other people notice and admire you","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"If television programs were not violent, they would not ________ in increased violence in the viewers.","a":"contribute","b":"result","c":"give","d":"conclude","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Result in sth: to make something happen [= cause].\u00a0\n.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"A few of the passengers were trying to get some sleep, but ________ of them were reading.","a":"almost","b":"all most","c":"most","d":"mostly","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Almost\/mostly is adverb.\u00a0\n- Most of sbd\/sth.\u00a0\n- Never say \"all most\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"A lot of the passengers were traveling home to ________ Christmas with their families.","a":"last","b":"hold","c":"keep","d":"spend","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Spend time etc with somebody: to use time doing a particular thing or pass time in a particular place.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Designing ________ for actors to wear requires a lot of creativity.","a":"scripts","b":"sets","c":"costumes","d":"kinds","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Costume: a set of clothes worn by an actor or by someone to make them look like something such as an animal, famous person etc.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The three men were found guilty ________ fraud.","a":"with","b":"for","c":"of","d":"by","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be\/Find guilty of sth\/doing sth: responsible for behaviour that is morally or socially unacceptable.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Every house in the street ________ the same.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs. Do not be misled by what follows of.\u00a0\n- To be: used to say that someone or something is the same as the subject of the sentence.\u00a0\n- To have: used to say what someone or something looks like, what qualities or features they possess.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Sociologists have long recognized that social tension _____.","a":"elements from group living.","b":"elements of a normal group life","c":"living are a group of elements.","d":"are normal elements of group life","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Recognize that + clause (S+ V+ O).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"}]}